afroleo.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy Policy » Afroleo- Daily Uniting Africans by Exchanging News, Ideas, Chats & Stories.

_Muicbook privacy policy_

This privacy policy sets out how Muicbook uses and protects any information that you give Muicbook when you use this website.   
Muicbook is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.   
Muicbook may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from year 2011. 

_Security_

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

___Links to other websites ___

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. 

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, we have given you full priviledge to correct the information.
